Phone: +1 647 896 6791

Aisyah Putri Megantari

20 Moselle Drive, Etobicoke, ON. M9V 5A7

ABOUT ME

Hi, My name is Aisyah and I currently work as a Drafter at Seif Designs. After graduating from the Interior Design Diploma program in 2019, I started my career as a Drafter in a small company. Within 6 months, I was given the opportunity to become an Interior Designer at a larger company. In 2020, I worked as an Assistant Lecturer in a public college's Associate degree program, while also doing freelance drafting work and on 2022 August i landed in. Canada as international student. My proficiency in AutoCAD (2016-202 versions) allows me to create technical drawings for cabinetry and interior design, while my skills in SketchUp, Maya, 3dsMax + Vray help me visualize designs. With years of experience, I am confident that I can contribute to your company's success.

EDUCATION CORE COMPETENCIES

Certificate

2022- Now

3d Modelling and Visual Effect Production Humber College North Campus

Associate Degree 2016-2019 Akademi Teknik PIKA, Indonesia

Make Up Artist 2021

Certification of Make up artist with Bianda Komala for my hobby

- Organizad
- Organized
- Detail Oriented
- Time management
- Computer Skills:
 (SketchUp, AutoCad, 3ds Max, Vray, Adobe Photoshop, Word, Maya, zBrush, Nuke, Houdini)

Email: megantariaisyah@gmail.com

- Work under pressure
- Fast learner
- Work well unsupervised

WORK EXPERIENCE

Cafe Clerk & Servers March 2017 - Sept 2017

Kurogi Cafe Coffe & Japanesse Eatery

As a part timer, Operate the Point of Sales (POS) computer and safely handle cash.

- -Maintain bar inventory by replenishing stock when needed from storage.
- -Maintain safe and healthy work environments by following company standard operating procedures.
- -Maintain a consistently clean and well-maintained sales floor and stock room.
- -Adhere to the cleaning schedule to prolong the life of all equipment. -Ocassionally a servers, provide an experienced server with a well attention to detail and

Drafter (Internship) Oct 2018 - Feb 2019

RSI Group

Internship college program for 4 and half month as a drafter.

- Creating technical drawings for interior and furniture and Presenting design detail drawings in 2D format using AutoCAD drafting software
- Demonstrating strong attention to detail and ensuring quality of work produced. Reviewing and revising technical drawings from superiors feedback,

Participating in design reviews and meetings to discuss project progres Maintaining project files and documentation in an organized manner.

Interior Designer & Drafter (Staff) March 2019 - Oct 2019

Lenny Indriani Design

As a Partimer while studying in college until graduating from College

- Designed a Interior space, Interior modeling using SketchUp and 3dsMax for rendering. Maintaining project files and documentation in an organized manner
- Interior space layout planning, and Interior drafting. Drawing include General plan, Section, Floor & Wall Finishes, Reflected Ceiling, Electrical plan.
- Demonstrating strong attention to detail and ensuring quality of work produced. Reviewing and revising technical drawings from superiors feedback, Participating in design reviews and meetings to discuss project progres.
- Conducting research on interior material specifications, Space planning within cabinetry, walk-in closets, built-in cabinets, and kitchens.

Interior Designer & Drafter (Staff) Nov 2

Nov 2019 - August 2020

APCONSULTANT

As a full time-staff,

- Designed a Interior space, Interior modeling using SketchUp and 3dsMax for rendering. Maintaining project files and documentation in an organized manner
- Interior space layout planning, and Interior drafting. Drawing include General plan, Section, Floor & Wall Finishes, Reflected Ceiling, Electrical plan.
- Demonstrating strong attention to detail and ensuring quality of work produced. Reviewing and revising technical drawings from superiors feedback, Participating in design reviews and meetings to discuss project progres.
- Conducting research on interior material specifications, Space planning within cabinetry, walk-in closets, built-in cabinets, and kitchens.

Assistant Lecturer (Staff)

Oct 2020 - June 2022

Furniture and Wood Processing Polytechnic (Politeknik Industri Furnitur Kendal)

For a period of 2 years, I had the opportunity to serve as an Assistant Lecturer at the Furniture and Woodworking Polytechnic, a Government international vocational school that specializes in furniture and wood processing. Assist student while learning AutoCad software and assist student assignment.

Drafter (Staff) Sept 2022 - Now

Seif Designs Inc. Toronto, ON

 $As a Part time \ drafter, i \ do \ mill working \ drawing \ for \ the \ company \ that \ run \ has \ mill work \ manufacture \ base \ on \ Toronto, \ ON.$

- Drew millwork technical drawing using AutoCad drafting software.
- Create Website for the Company, Seif Designs current website.
- Create 2d cabinetry design visual for client using AutoCad.- Create Drafting Drawing Template for the Company.